[
  {
    "question": "According to existentialist philosophy, which philosopher is best known for the concept of \"existence precedes essence?\"",
    "choice1": "Immanuel Kant",
    "choice2": "Jean-Jacques Rousseau",
    "choice3": "Jean-Paul Sartre",
    "choice4": "Friedrich Nietzsche",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "In ethics, which moral theory is based on the principle that the right action is the one that maximizes overall happiness or pleasure?",
    "choice1": "Deontology",
    "choice2": "Virtue Ethics",
    "choice3": "Utilitarianism",
    "choice4": "Existentialism",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "In epistemology, what is the philosophical position that knowledge is primarily or exclusively derived from experience?",
    "choice1": "Rationalism",
    "choice2": "Empiricism",
    "choice3": "Idealism",
    "choice4": "Skepticism",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the central concept in existentialist philosophy, emphasizing individual freedom and responsibility?",
    "choice1": "Utilitarianism",
    "choice2": "Determinism",
    "choice3": "Absurdism",
    "choice4": "Nihilism",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the central concept in existentialism that emphasizes individual freedom and the responsibility of individuals to create their own meaning in life?",
    "choice1": "Determinism",
    "choice2": "Nihilism",
    "choice3": "Absurdism",
    "choice4": "Existential Authenticity",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the central concept of existentialism?",
    "choice1": "Utilitarianism",
    "choice2": "Absurdism",
    "choice3": "Dualism",
    "choice4": "Determinism",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the philosopher known for the concept of the \"veil of ignorance\" in the context of justice?",
    "choice1": "Immanuel Kant",
    "choice2": "Jean-Jacques Rousseau",
    "choice3": "John Rawls",
    "choice4": "John Stuart Mill",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "In Eastern philosophy, which school of thought emphasizes the concept of non-attachment and the path to enlightenment through self-realization?",
    "choice1": "Confucianism",
    "choice2": "Taoism",
    "choice3": "Zen Buddhism",
    "choice4": "Shinto",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "In African philosophy, which term refers to the concept of a life force or spiritual energy that permeates the universe and all living things?",
    "choice1": "Ashé",
    "choice2": "Ubuntu",
    "choice3": "Maat",
    "choice4": "Kaitiakitanga",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Which ancient Greek philosopher is known for his teachings on skepticism, including the idea that knowledge is elusive and that we should suspend judgment in the absence of certainty?",
    "choice1": "Socrates",
    "choice2": "Plato",
    "choice3": "Aristotle",
    "choice4": "Pyrrho",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "In Islamic philosophy, which medieval philosopher is known for his synthesis of Greek philosophy, particularly the works of Aristotle, with Islamic theology?",
    "choice1": "Avicenna (Ibn Sina)",
    "choice2": "Al-Farabi",
    "choice3": "Al-Ghazali",
    "choice4": "Averroes (Ibn Rushd)",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Meaning of the word \"Philosophy\"",
    "choice1": "Lover of questions",
    "choice2": "Lover of soapboxes",
    "choice3": "Lover of philosophy",
    "choice4": "Love of wisdom",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "The allegory of the cave argues what?",
    "choice1": "We are born with infinite knowledge",
    "choice2": "Our perceptions may not be accurate",
    "choice3": "Perceptions are sources of absolute knowledge",
    "choice4": "There is value in ignorance",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is widely known as the first existentialist, despite never having used the word existentialism?",
    "choice1": "Søren Kierkegaard",
    "choice2": "Hannah Arendt",
    "choice3": "Alan Watts",
    "choice4": "Jean-Paul Sartre",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "According to Plato, what is knowledge?",
    "choice1": "A justified true belief",
    "choice2": "There is no such thing as true knowledge",
    "choice3": "That which can be proven",
    "choice4": "Opinion",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Metaphysics is the study of...",
    "choice1": "Knowledge",
    "choice2": "Ethics",
    "choice3": "Politics",
    "choice4": "Existence",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the philosophical study of value called?",
    "choice1": "Ethics",
    "choice2": "Axiology",
    "choice3": "Valuation",
    "choice4": "Ontology",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "Plato was a student to which philosopher?",
    "choice1": "Aristotle",
    "choice2": "Thomas Aquinas",
    "choice3": "Xenophon",
    "choice4": "Socrates",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "Epistemology is the theory of...",
    "choice1": "Cosmology",
    "choice2": "Poetics",
    "choice3": "Knowledge",
    "choice4": "Metaphysics",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Which branch of philosophy deals with the question of beauty?",
    "choice1": "Decorum",
    "choice2": "Dramatics",
    "choice3": "Poetics",
    "choice4": "Aesthetics",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "In Japanese philosophy, which concept refers to the aesthetic appreciation of impermanence and the transient nature of beauty, often associated with cherry blossoms?",
    "choice1": "Wabi-sabi",
    "choice2": "Kintsugi",
    "choice3": "Ikebana",
    "choice4": "Satori",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "In African philosophy, which concept embodies the communal values and interconnectedness of individuals within a community, emphasizing the importance of relationships and shared humanity?",
    "choice1": "Itutu",
    "choice2": "Ashé",
    "choice3": "Maat",
    "choice4": "Ubuntu",
    "answer": 4
  }
]